[
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "And the earth",
        "pcklId": "455",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْأَرْضِ ذَاتِ الصَّدْعِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "rootWordId": 78,
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلْيَنْظُرِ الْإِنْسَانُ مِمَّ خُلِقَ",
        "rootWord": "أ ن س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِنسَٰن",
        "waznEnglish": "you perceive",
        "waznTlit": "insān",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْلَى",
        "answer": "will be tested",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "rootWordId": 158,
        "tlit": "tub'lā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَ تُبْلَى السَّرَائِرُ",
        "rootWord": "ب ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَلَوْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to test",
        "waznTlit": "balaw",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "rootWordId": 173,
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " يَخْرُجُ مِنْ بَيْنِ الصُّلْبِ وَالتَّرَائِبِ",
        "rootWord": "ب ي ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَيْن",
        "waznEnglish": "to make clear",
        "waznTlit": "bayn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالتَّرَائِبِ",
        "answer": "and the ribs",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 179,
        "tlit": "wal-tarāibi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "5",
        "arabicAyah": " يَخْرُجُ مِنْ بَيْنِ الصُّلْبِ وَالتَّرَائِبِ",
        "rootWord": "ت ر ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تَّرَآئِب",
        "waznEnglish": "well-matched",
        "waznTlit": "tarāib",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّاقِبُ",
        "answer": "the piercing",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 203,
        "tlit": "l-thāqibu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " النَّجْمُ الثَّاقِبُ",
        "rootWord": "ث ق ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ث ق ب",
        "waznEnglish": "the piercing",
        "waznTlit": "thā qāf bā",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَافِظٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a protector",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "rootWordId": 339,
        "tlit": "ḥāfiẓun",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنْ كُلُّ نَفْسٍ لَمَّا عَلَيْهَا حَافِظٌ",
        "rootWord": "ح ف ظ",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "حَٰفِظ",
        "waznEnglish": "(orders) them to guard",
        "waznTlit": "ḥāfiẓ",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "Coming forth",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "rootWordId": 397,
        "tlit": "yakhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " يَخْرُجُ مِنْ بَيْنِ الصُّلْبِ وَالتَّرَائِبِ",
        "rootWord": "خ ر ج",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَرَجَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to go out, to come out, to depart, to leave",
        "waznTlit": "kharaja",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِقَ",
        "answer": "he is created",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "rootWordId": 431,
        "tlit": "khuliqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلْيَنْظُرِ الْإِنْسَانُ مِمَّ خُلِقَ",
        "rootWord": "خ ل ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَلَقَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to create",
        "waznTlit": "khalaqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلِقَ",
        "answer": "He is created",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "rootWordId": 431,
        "tlit": "khuliqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " خُلِقَ مِنْ مَاءٍ دَافِقٍ",
        "rootWord": "خ ل ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَلَقَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to create",
        "waznTlit": "khalaqa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدْرَاكَ",
        "answer": "can make you know",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "rootWordId": 469,
        "tlit": "adrāka",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا أَدْرَاكَ مَا الطَّارِقُ",
        "rootWord": "د ر ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَدْرَىٰ",
        "waznEnglish": "to make known",
        "waznTlit": "adrā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَافِقٍ",
        "answer": "ejected",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 477,
        "tlit": "dāfiqin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " خُلِقَ مِنْ مَاءٍ دَافِقٍ",
        "rootWord": "د ف ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "د ف ق",
        "waznEnglish": "ejected",
        "waznTlit": "dāl fā qāf",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجْعِهِ",
        "answer": "return him",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "rootWordId": 536,
        "tlit": "rajʿihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ عَلَىٰ رَجْعِهِ لَقَادِرٌ",
        "rootWord": "ر ج ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَجْع",
        "waznEnglish": "[they] will not return",
        "waznTlit": "rajʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّجْعِ",
        "answer": "returns",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "rootWordId": 536,
        "tlit": "l-rajʿi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالسَّمَاءِ ذَاتِ الرَّجْعِ",
        "rootWord": "ر ج ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَجْع",
        "waznEnglish": "[they] will not return",
        "waznTlit": "rajʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُوَيْدًا",
        "answer": "little",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "rootWordId": 600,
        "tlit": "ruwaydan",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَهِّلِ الْكَافِرِينَ أَمْهِلْهُمْ رُوَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "ر و د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رُوَيْد",
        "waznEnglish": "And sought to seduce him",
        "waznTlit": "ruwayd",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّرَائِرُ",
        "answer": "the secrets",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "rootWordId": 681,
        "tlit": "l-sarāiru",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَ تُبْلَى السَّرَائِرُ",
        "rootWord": "س ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَّرَآئِر",
        "waznEnglish": "pleasing",
        "waznTlit": "sarāir",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "By the sky",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "wal-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالسَّمَاءِ وَالطَّارِقِ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "By the sky",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "rootWordId": 726,
        "tlit": "wal-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "11",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالسَّمَاءِ ذَاتِ الرَّجْعِ",
        "rootWord": "س م و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "سَمَآء",
        "waznEnglish": "[I] (have) named her",
        "waznTlit": "samā",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّدْعِ",
        "answer": "cracks open",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 828,
        "tlit": "l-ṣadʿi",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "12",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالْأَرْضِ ذَاتِ الصَّدْعِ",
        "rootWord": "ص د ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صَّدْع",
        "waznEnglish": "So proclaim",
        "waznTlit": "ṣadʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّلْبِ",
        "answer": "the backbone",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 853,
        "tlit": "l-ṣul'bi",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "7",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " يَخْرُجُ مِنْ بَيْنِ الصُّلْبِ وَالتَّرَائِبِ",
        "rootWord": "ص ل ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صُّلْب",
        "waznEnglish": "they crucified him",
        "waznTlit": "ṣul'b",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالطَّارِقِ",
        "answer": "and the night comer",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "rootWordId": 909,
        "tlit": "wal-ṭāriqi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "1",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَالسَّمَاءِ وَالطَّارِقِ",
        "rootWord": "ط ر ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَّارِق",
        "waznEnglish": "(to) a way",
        "waznTlit": "ṭāriq",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّارِقُ",
        "answer": "the night comer (is)",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "rootWordId": 909,
        "tlit": "l-ṭāriqu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "2",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا أَدْرَاكَ مَا الطَّارِقُ",
        "rootWord": "ط ر ق",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَّارِق",
        "waznEnglish": "(to) a way",
        "waznTlit": "ṭāriq",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصْلٌ",
        "answer": "decisive",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "rootWordId": 1135,
        "tlit": "faṣlun",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلٌ فَصْلٌ",
        "rootWord": "ف ص ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "فَصْل",
        "waznEnglish": "set out",
        "waznTlit": "faṣl",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Adjective)"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَادِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) Able",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "rootWordId": 1181,
        "tlit": "laqādirun",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "8",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ عَلَىٰ رَجْعِهِ لَقَادِرٌ",
        "rootWord": "ق د ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَادِر",
        "waznEnglish": "they have control",
        "waznTlit": "qādir",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَقَوْلٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a Word",
        "pcklId": "1716",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "laqawlun",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "13",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُ لَقَوْلٌ فَصْلٌ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَوْل",
        "waznEnglish": "say",
        "waznTlit": "qawl",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "power",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "rootWordId": 1247,
        "tlit": "quwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "4",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَا لَهُ مِنْ قُوَّةٍ وَلَا نَاصِرٍ",
        "rootWord": "ق و ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قُوَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) All-Strong",
        "waznTlit": "quwwat",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "512",
        "rootWordId": 1280,
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَهِّلِ الْكَافِرِينَ أَمْهِلْهُمْ رُوَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "ك ف ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَٰفِرُون",
        "waznEnglish": "disbelieve[d]",
        "waznTlit": "kāfirūn",
        "waznType": "Active participle (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "(is) every",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "rootWordId": 1288,
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنْ كُلُّ نَفْسٍ لَمَّا عَلَيْهَا حَافِظٌ",
        "rootWord": "ك ل ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كُلّ",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) a burden",
        "waznTlit": "kull",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "are plotting",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "rootWordId": 1307,
        "tlit": "yakīdūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُمْ يَكِيدُونَ كَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "ك ي د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِيدُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to scheme, to plot, to plan",
        "waznTlit": "kīdu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكِيدُ",
        "answer": "But I am planning",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "rootWordId": 1307,
        "tlit": "wa-akīdu",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "16",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَكِيدُ كَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "ك ي د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كِيدُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to scheme, to plot, to plan",
        "waznTlit": "kīdu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدًا",
        "answer": "a plot",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "rootWordId": 1307,
        "tlit": "kaydan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "15",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنَّهُمْ يَكِيدُونَ كَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "ك ي د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَيْد",
        "waznEnglish": "scheme against me",
        "waznTlit": "kayd",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدًا",
        "answer": "a plan",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "rootWordId": 1307,
        "tlit": "kaydan",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "16",
        "wordnum": "2",
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَكِيدُ كَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "ك ي د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَيْد",
        "waznEnglish": "scheme against me",
        "waznTlit": "kayd",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَهِّلِ",
        "answer": "So give respite",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 1422,
        "tlit": "famahhili",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَهِّلِ الْكَافِرِينَ أَمْهِلْهُمْ رُوَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "م ه ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَهِّلِ",
        "waznEnglish": "to give respite",
        "waznTlit": "mahhili",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْهِلْهُمْ",
        "answer": "Give respite to them ",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 1422,
        "tlit": "amhil'hum",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "17",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَهِّلِ الْكَافِرِينَ أَمْهِلْهُمْ رُوَيْدًا",
        "rootWord": "م ه ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَمْهِلْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to give respite",
        "waznTlit": "amhil",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءٍ",
        "answer": "a water",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "rootWordId": 1428,
        "tlit": "māin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "6",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " خُلِقَ مِنْ مَاءٍ دَافِقٍ",
        "rootWord": "م و ه",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "م و ه",
        "waznEnglish": "water",
        "waznTlit": "mīm wāw hā",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّجْمُ",
        "answer": "(It is) the star",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "rootWordId": 1444,
        "tlit": "al-najmu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "3",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " النَّجْمُ الثَّاقِبُ",
        "rootWord": "ن ج م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ن ج م",
        "waznEnglish": "the stars",
        "waznTlit": "nūn jīm mīm",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِرٍ",
        "answer": "any helper",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "rootWordId": 1477,
        "tlit": "nāṣirin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "10",
        "wordnum": "6",
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَا لَهُ مِنْ قُوَّةٍ وَلَا نَاصِرٍ",
        "rootWord": "ن ص ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَاصِر",
        "waznEnglish": "will be helped",
        "waznTlit": "nāṣir",
        "waznType": "Active participle"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَنْظُرِ",
        "answer": "So let see",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "rootWordId": 1487,
        "tlit": "falyanẓuri",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "5",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " فَلْيَنْظُرِ الْإِنْسَانُ مِمَّ خُلِقَ",
        "rootWord": "ن ظ ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَّظَرَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to look, to see",
        "waznTlit": "naẓara",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "294",
        "rootWordId": 1500,
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "4",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " إِنْ كُلُّ نَفْسٍ لَمَّا عَلَيْهَا حَافِظٌ",
        "rootWord": "ن ف س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "نَفْس",
        "waznEnglish": "self, soul, person, mind",
        "waznTlit": "nafs",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهَزْلِ",
        "answer": "(is) for amusement",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1552,
        "tlit": "bil-hazli",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "14",
        "wordnum": "3",
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَا هُوَ بِالْهَزْلِ",
        "rootWord": "ه ز ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ه ز ل",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) for amusement",
        "waznTlit": "hā zāy lām",
        "waznType": "Noun"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "rootWordId": 1664,
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surahnum": "86",
        "ayahnum": "9",
        "wordnum": "1",
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَ تُبْلَى السَّرَائِرُ",
        "rootWord": "ي و م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ي و م",
        "waznEnglish": "(of the) Day",
        "waznTlit": "yā wāw mīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)"
    }
]